and today is the twenty-third
these little acrylic things here are selling
old fuck
the box went down right
but investment in strategy
is on
I'm confident
important is this
to win the war you don't have to kill the soldier
rather find who the general is in the prospect
one by one
I'll call the client the right soldier
general
you win the war
is on
connects to the idea
this strategy here i call the Trojan horse
this one ó
thick bending
one by one
general
you will already understand this o
arrive there
this one ó
is the normal model
we do what
wastes a lot of time trying
to a customer to be able to sell our service
your product
one who speaks no
other speaks no
another speaks yes
instead of me selling
truffle and taking away one by one
trying to convince a person to sell a truffle
i prefer to do what
find the right person
then you use the entire network and earn a lot more money
in less time
through this guy here you will make money
come to me that I show you in practice
it's crazy you locked it in that our clothes
I will send 1 vial
it's crazy bro
I exchanged that idea there
was not
EU spoke pro
pro 2 has how to pull over there already leave 1
now i'm here at Vavá's barbershop mano
the cousin already said I will
take a homie
oh that gives time
oh no
the noise is rolling or not
you are connected somewhere
as soon as EU manages to leave the truffles in this format
also that I also have to work on the turn
understood
I left
forty
don't worry that the thing here is straight
anything
if you need it give me hello
that I come here and collected
I didn't even get there man
my partner here has already joined
already finished the truffle
sky bro
I got bigger rain here to leave
is closed
in addition to being beautiful passive you have to think about it bro
or raining like hell here
if i depended on my direct sale in one to one bro
i would shatter have a lost day
passive income
it's the channel
I'm exchanging an idea here with you
guess bro
piquezinho
that's it brother
secret is you pick up your strategy
and put in the right place
pum finished my brother
she makes herself
it's on man
ah cannon
but the guys won't let me put
my truffle there and winning nothing
how do you do
in my case
I clean showcase for free Guy
so i change
please
uncle exchange currency
this is very important
ok people
until tomorrow
and if you want to know a little more
how it works or
Trojan horse and others
strategies
i have an e book with several
sales strategies there for you we go
that we go
haha